Come to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
The rhythm, yeah, yeah, yeah, flow
Hearts in the balance, every card an open door
Feel the romance in every arcane lord
your background noise with an ego to fill to miss
Okay, I'm back. Okay, sorry
My Alex is sure loud, isn't he loud?
Yeah, I mean, I don't know if I'll get I can get in trouble. I was just hearing some people had their streams
Had their streams deleted, you know for talking
About certain things. So hey, hey. Oh, wow. Cool or Vader gong gong gong gong. Yeah guys, okay, so the oh you like the new
And also the emojis guys there's like one if you want a reading you can put the crystal ball emoji if you want to
Just be here for chaos. You can put the skull emoji
There's also a
SOS emoji. Can you help?
Okay, I smile I yeah, you can play around with them. I have 14 14 emojis in there now I
can get more
When I hit a hundred
Nothing we say we get a hit, but you get it. We got you hit. Oh, yeah, I know. I know
and then Alex but Alex kind of brings a
More attention to it and I just I wanted to change the energy, but it was fun. It was fun. And it's kind of I
Don't know much about politics. So I don't
Can't really you want peace won't promise forever. Well, sure you're
You're an agent of chaos goes
I'll get my link up too.
I did a really cool, I did a really cool new graphic
for Thursday, that's not so Thursday
for another few minutes, so I won't post it yet.
But yeah, let's see, I'll get the link pinned.
What do you mean agent?
It's an agent, like an agent, like you work for...
Disorder, okay, let me see
Okay
Yeah
You people are buzzing on peasant. Okay. Yeah, well, let's let's say a prayer for everybody. Okay. I don't like it
Okay, so
Yeah, I think I have some
Here we go starting
Hello
Hi brother
What's up with you?
How are you the Asian of chaos?
Yes, my favorite mr. Ghostie
It's a little ghost. How are you? How's it good? How's it going tonight?
It's actually good because I
You know I cleaned up my house today. I did my laundry. I did my dishes. It's like I'm feeling productive
pretty good
Nice accomplished. I know it's been there's just been
Even if there's like, you know, even if there's like even if there's like, oh, I got a couple water bottles
You know, I was I was gonna get them yesterday, but I do it then you do it
You always feel a little bit, you know, a little bit better about doing it
And no, it's not that hard to do but it's like I seem to procrastinate a lot about stuff, right?
It's like I procrastinate everything and then I say I'm like, oh, but it feels so much better
Oh one water bottle of turns on the two two turns in the four four turns in the eight
Well, that's why I drink only be only beer and energy drinks fuck water
The water why I just
Was I just look down and look like you were lighting that shit from your finger
The water is turning the frogs gay right now. Do you know about that?
How much water have you had in your life, sir?
I've never had a sip of it not one sip
But I'm talking about the you know the water they're serving in tap water with all the plastic and stuff that it gets into the water
There's all these chemicals these are weird
Making everyone want to experiment with y'all with the same sex, right? What around here man when I drink that like fucking
Like restaurant water this it eats me up. You know, I'll be pooping for like two days
Yeah, who pings
Yeah, no violently
Well, I wouldn't I wouldn't
Help me smile really. Oh, you'd like it. I got you. I think they're using that mountain water
I don't think they're using no fucking man. I think there's getting straight from the off the screen
I like I like avion, but you know
Desani water comes out of a filtration plant comes out of the Coca-Cola's filtration plant
So it's like the same water these the coke basically, which is this filter sewage water and it's fascinating. I
Like cold water my brother drinks room temperature water. I've never got it
I don't like I've never understood why. Hi. Hi. You scared the shit out of me. Did I sorry? Yeah, I'm sorry
He's so quiet, and then it's like a hello
I'm doing good. How are you doing?
I had a big key
It's a little do you want to say hi to the shot? Hi, pretty kitty
Huxley pissed off Asian of chaos. He always
She always has RBF and she's happy. She's happy. You like being pet like that
Hi, look at that pretty cat. It's that pretty cat. I'll put you down here
Go sit back up here. She was behind me on the couch. There's Catnip all up there. Wow. Trevor is that you Trevor?
Are you Trevor? Trevor Trevor in the chat? Let me see or from the panel
Yeah, you know, what's funny is that on the chat GPT, it's like it came up with the concept of my show
I didn't put the word chaos in there, but it came up with chaos on its own
It was like it said so it says it called my panel like that's why it's a chaos like divine chaos on this
Drawing I have that are that it made of me. Let's see if I have that still
Dude, I've joined gamers that that are live streaming and when you join like there's the AI like what the topic is about
And I've seen some crazy ass like description though, but like they've not seen that at all
Like they might have said one thing and then like oh, that's like what in the world?
Yeah, I think some crazy ass topics
I would bring up examples were on YouTube and think I'm thinking about extreme stuff like it's like what are you talking about?
No one even mentioned that
Oh, yeah, so this picture right here. See it says it just came up with this chat. She came up with that
I look very serious. What a handsome man. You you're handsome, but you look very
You're gonna read the fuck out of some tarot cards in the second
Very serious. Yeah, but it's interesting picture and it says it's such a sacred chaos and it came up with that
I don't know it also remembers what it says to you and so it it will say
Like a lot of like stuff that you've already said to it
And it will like tie in jokes and it makes all these jokes about Rudy and the cats and stuff like that
Your AI
Am I AI?
Yes. Oh like you think I'm fake. No, I'm in bed. Oh, oh shit turn it off. Never mind
The AI doesn't turn off
Everywhere we're like everywhere for an off button, but we're not gonna fight. It's kidding. Okay. Thank you. Okay. Hold on
Sorry, what does that mean? What does that mean Thomas Dell my cock?
Okay, so Thomas Dell is gonna be hidden from the chat because he's saying I'm stolen Valor for whatever reason you are now
What Valor you still on me? I asked their persona non grata persona non grata is a poor wishes there me see
Um, okay. Yep. Oh, okay. So, wow, look at all the cool emojis. They come out really
cool. The goat, the evil eye. Oh, I love a ghost. Oh, go. Yeah. I am the goat, you.
Oh, yeah. I have, oh, we have a new guest. Hold on one second. Let's make sure. Hello.
Hello. Hello. Hello. This is Justine Kesner. I'm Ziggy's friend. Okay. Hi.
Hello, thank you for your full government. Hey, what's your social security number real quick? No, no, no, no, please don't give it
Please don't give it. No, I I'm from Canadian. We have a sin number
Can I get it? Please don't share that either, please
Okay, okay, so my name is first name first will last name go some psyches friend
Yeah, there's a missus spunky. Yes, buddy. Hi. Justine. I'm spunky
Do you want to know something really funny, you know what's funky means in England?
Yes, I do
But I've had this screen name for like 20 years
I mean
I'm just you see wise. Okay. Okay. There's another ghost. Hold on. What's going on?
Oh, there can only be one ghost. This is the real ghost.
Who the fuck is this guy? There can only be one real ghost, brother.
There's gotta be one ghost, brother. I don't like this guy.
Alright, who's this guy? Obviously, you're below me, sir.
Obviously. Alright. Is this Robert Kennedy? Is this Robert Kennedy again? I'm not sure.
There can only be one ghost, brother.
Where's this guy from? I don't like his voice. It sounds annoying.
Where are you from? I don't like your voice.
I don't know. I don't know.
Do you want to know something?
Robert Kennedy. Let me ask this
myself. Specialist man and what
you guys should be so proud that
you had a Robert Kennedy. See,
you need to be watching out for
this woman right now because
she's not the real Robert Kennedy.
It was an impersonator.
She's teaching you the real
I don't understand your gay language. Well, then you're not the real ghost
You don't say the burning fruits on you dumb dumb
Or say dumb dumb for me. I
Don't know who this guy is
It's just seen God with a voice changer. No, no, no, no just seems real
Yeah, I'm here. I'm real. Okay. All right, summer
I'm just being quiet because
Have you ever just teens my woman now, have you have you dated Ziggy? Hold on if you dated Ziggy
Yes, I I don't know. Sure. Okay, how we
How was he's a boyfriend or is he as a boyfriend? He's an amazing person. You know what? He's got a very kind heart
He actually has a very kind heart and when he was with his chickens, he kisses them and he is very nice
Did you just date him online or in person?
the online
You haven't met in person
And you said you dated him come on baby girl
The real ghost don't hang out women in this gig fake ghost guys
Spunky. Oh, shit. Never mind.
Now, this is summer talking.
This is summer talking to you.
And you said you only seen half of them.
That's what you said the first time.
That's not even a close-up.
No, I've seen it.
I've seen it already.
I've seen the top half and the bottom half.
Girl, get yourself a seat.
Work on your self-esteem.
Ziggy, did you send her nude photos of yourself?
And why haven't you sent me any?
Oh, no. Hell no.
Oh
Come to find out
You will kill me on land they're like, oh we had a relationship, but I've never even seen it. I'm like what the fuck
Girl you backtrackin I don't really care. I don't think it's weird
It was a body if you never even like see them offline you never
And just because you see the top of his head, how long did you all date Olan?
I find this intriguing.
We don't date.
She said you all did.
No.
I'd like to.
No, no, no, no, you said you dated
So you fuck the man online
Who is it?
I don't know who I want to do.
How are you fucking him and he's not even seeing him?
I don't know you.
That's what I wanted to do, and that's all I want to do.
Thanks.
Thanks for the two things.
Well, you can't fuck somebody.
You can't fuck somebody online, sweetie.
Summer, shut up.
I want to know you.
No, I'm married
Of course you are 17 years
Hold on Ziggy, please I'm not trying to be mean I promise you I'm not
Summer, I'd rather be a friend than a foe, okay?
I will.
I mean, I don't know if you can have you as a friend.
I don't know you to have you as a friend.
I don't know you to know you to have you as a friend.
She lives in Canada, so her feelings are going to be more...
I'm not being made, I'm asking questions and she can't deal with that.
She'll only be able to fuck an internet.
I just didn't explain why she fucked a man, she only seen half of the space.
I
Need a summer that's what I mean. Do anything ask me anything. I'm an open okay
So you couldn't you seem like a sweet girl. You really seem like a sweet girl. Yeah, I am I am a very nice girl at that
Yes
Okay, why wouldn't you get with somebody around me? I can't talk to you if you're gonna over talk and you can't hear the question
Like summer is what I'm saying
I have a man and everything. I'm completely fine. Me and Ziggy just have fun together.
Is he real? That's all we have. Yes.
Like me and him, we just have fun together. It's just fun. All right?
So you're literally cheating on him with AI?
So you're a cheater?
No, we're just having fun. There's no, there's no baby girl. I'm just going off what you're saying. That's it
So you guys like virtually like jump up together
Every once in a while like I'll jump in now you're annoying, bro
There's just a lot of amazing women online that like I don't understand why you all don't like meet somebody by you
So you can like have a connection and go out on dinner and have them over at your house
There's a lot of other dating guys. They've never even fucking seen on live like what in the fuck is wrong with you?
Oh, I know back in the day
And then I got fucking over it and now it's my I got my neighbor
That's good. I mean, I mean, you know, even if you like I'm not gonna say I haven't before I got married to stuff
That's it. I dated something I dated people in other states and stuff like that
But like I could meet them I could you know to me like we could go on a date
We could had spent some time together not just online. I mean why yes, you can have an emotional connection
Eventually you want to I don't know hang out with the person through it
So I just found it odd that you had said you all dated so you all did and you guys are just friends and you flirt
Yeah, that's pretty much I didn't get that at all. I think she doesn't know
What she's explaining now, I think when it first came out it came out
Disorder I'm socially I have a social anxiety and so sometimes I talk a bit gibberish
I'm nervous.
I'm trying to crash out.
You're nervous.
Yeah, I just want to be happy up here and I want to have fun.
You guys hear me. What do you expect?
I'm summer nice to meet you beautiful
It's nice to use summer. I'm gonna be summer now
my favorite
Scooter song is summer and I love that song since 1993 and
Scooter is an amazing
Electronica band from Germany and I fucking love them
Well, I'll say that I have a lot of
Fucking music, sorry. I have a lot of friends that living Canada that are absolutely amazing. So summer summer. What piggy?
Do you understand?
What is happening?
Five minutes I've heard summer fucking five hundred times
Stop saying summer don't ever tell somebody to shut the fuck up dude
I'm telling you, I'm asking summer. Do you like me to explain why?
Here
Go
She did
Yeah, we are you got you got Paige on you out. You know you're doing bad
You'll understand I'm Canadian and so some of our stings are not your saying. Yo, hey, just Canadian and so am I
Canadian corner over here. Fuck you
You know what? I don't even think you're Canadian
I'm near a thank you
You're no you're near a fucking mental breakdown
I'm one of my I have a bunch of friends that live in a live up in Canada. So I think I want to come
Are you summer and you answered that I'm out of British almost Canadian
Summer and she said
I'm from British Columbia, but I live in Alberta.
There we go.
I live in Alberta.
At my bad page, I didn't mean to do that.
I was going to be like, page is up there too.
She's awesome.
That's the thing.
No, no, that's what you weren't listening.
I'm from Canada.
She she lives in Alberta. I live in Alberta and we have to be like, you know, we have to just meet
Wait, so you live in Australia or Alberta? No, I live in the Canada
Canada
This is what I hear from Canadians. It's Alberta. Like I don't know
Isn't there there's four probably sweet time about what do you mean?
You're gonna what are you saying about my woman?
That's nothing why are they just sounded ditching us as we had you know what I'm saying about your woman
She can do better
You better watch it you better watch that now
Oh, you'll say that you got a
Son of a bitch if you talk about her again, I'll get more drunk
That's what Eminem said, he said,
You want me to watch my mouth, how you want me to turn my eyeballs and turn the fuck around?
That's my woman!
Yeah
Both of them are my
What makes them your women may have native people all the time and we sound
money money
Well, that's a good fucking answer brother
I was looking for a debate, but I was a good fucking answer
Yeah, I could put you in a fucking RV or fucking what the fuck I gave you that one that was funny
Let that be an example and trust me I know is why you don't go on the internet drunk
Go on the internet drunk all the time
fuck yeah i fucking love it i even know ziggie enough to know he goes on
the internet drunk all the time fuck yeah i love it and i don't even know ziggie
it's uh dude it's an online fucking fucking love it
someone knows me that's why you know what i do like i mean i know i already know
oh yeah dubs is also another one that comes on and and gets a little sometimes tipsy online
I smoke pot. Not it. Not me. I'm smoking pot in the fucking RV. Oh, yeah, you do go because you
test me out every time you're trying to go. Man issue. I'm smoking 95% and I go we the front
I love weed. Weed is good.
I hate weed.
I think I'm like the only, I think I'm the only person. No, there's my other brother and fucking we hate weed
Wait, oh, yeah, we're talking a small motion. Maybe we'd hate to you. Did you ever think?
Exactly, exactly boys talking at 2.5. Yeah, dude. No, I'm telling you I can't fucking smoke weed even fucking
Yeah. Nothing small. Yeah.
So, it's summer. She she she
kind of understands where I've
been in life now. Imagine that
and me smoking weed and I have
hyper like when I smoke weed
now, it used to be a very big
but now when I smoke it, I get
hyper vigilant.
And if you've seen yeah, you don't even know
You get my drunk ass
Did you did you say did you smoke sativa?
Because maybe you're smoking the wrong weed because sometimes I know I burnt pretty good though
And back in the day I used to smoke sativa now I smoke indica and it's a way better for me
I'm just what have you ever heard of the other
Is that common
I smoke cash. I smoke black tar hash back in the day.
Whoa, whoa, black tar heroin.
Black tar heroin.
Oh, yeah.
What the fuck?
Yes, black tar hash we get a heroine
She was talking about weed
No
She doesn't know what she's saying.
All right, Nali, let's stop.
Dumb dumb.
Don't call her dum-dum. She's okay
I'm not trying hey, I'm not trying to find anybody
I
Wasn't talking to her. I was talking to you dumb dumb
Okay, I'd rather take sir man penis you get where I'm you get where I'm going. I was talking to you
That guy over there if you dig up the bones in a hundred years. Where are you gonna identify as you're gonna defy as a male
How can you?
Yeah, I
You want to break it down even more for you, so I'll do it for you, but I'm gonna hold on
Oh, we're not bashing people but they believe are we?
No, it depends what they believe. I mean if you come up here
Go ahead sir
Well, this is yeah, I mean
If you believe like, you know the legend of like though that's probably real life or probably gonna bash you
I'm not gonna lie to you. I'm gonna ask you. We'll accept you
But we're men though like we get
No, I mean, hey, I don't want to lie to you. Hey, don't assume my gender
Appreciate you asking me sir
You've been drinking too much soy latte, bro, okay
of what that was a claim and of the burden of proof on you how do I why do I sound like that go ahead
of the burns on me
that was a guy that is you made the claim
that you made a claim you know how do you make it all
How do you sound like you fucking feel so confident?
Listen, don't cut me off after you ask me a question.
How do you sound like you drink too much soy latte?
Go ahead and speak again, just a couple words.
you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you
oh you stop talking and actually answer the question oh my god so the answer to my question would be
your poor little buddy but my question was who am i attacking who am i attacking the soy police
I
Listen bro, I'm only just pulling your fucking leg as you were kind of being aggressive and I had to let you know
Yeah, and that's check you really look a separate check your ass
That sounds kind of stop talking to me. I just checked you
The burden of proof is on you
I checked you
And you said the same thing like oh the burden of proof beyond me
I didn't call you gay, I never called you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay, I did not call you gay,
You have absolutely no idea. I didn't call you gay
Women I didn't call you
One time that I call you gay
There's hot chicks on the friggin thing and they want to argue yeah crazy
Look summer you're married
You're my brother anyway, so
Here's if they're beautiful. Well, you said
You not talk shit to your own brother, I don't know if you have brothers, but do you not talk shit?
Yeah, I do because they're younger than me. Yep
Meaning
Anyhoo, what's that page? How's your day been? Did she leave where our girl goes? She left?
There he goes
Dang
Somebody's chat over page's face. That's kind of fucked up
Put me over there
Yeah
No, we can leave me where I am probably
Like
Well, how do you say Alberta and Alberta?
No, cuz I know a lot of Canadians
You can't argue with her she lives in Alberta
From Alberta Canada, I get it, but you're gonna argue with a woman from Alberta on how to say Alberta come on
Well, yeah
She's more American than you guys might think
Answer her language. She doesn't have that she doesn't have that
Hey, you know
How many times have you had a conversation with Paige? I love you, but like come on dude a number of times actually
I'll be up here in Alberta. I'm not talking smack about her
that's funny because that is something we would say
Alberta
Nope, not like that, ever
Oh, no he says
Maybe you pronounce it, uh, Dong Dong
They pronounce it, and then they say, Bertha
I don't like the role, sorry
I can show you Alberta Audits like he does it all the time
A bunch of people do it
That's about right
For sure
Brightest, have you ever been to Brightest, Columbia?
Yeah, I'm from there. I just live here. Yeah, and then there's Ontario. Yeah
Yeah, Manitoba is a nice spot
Yes, matter of fact, I'm about to uh, I'm about to mention one out of
Sound fresh just by speaking what am I gonna say
It's pretty funny though because everyone says then there's cubic if you're been to cubic it's funny because it's not
But it's called cubic no, but I've rolled some shit and some Cubans before
That little bit of honey on that shit that should smoke forever
Raven do you mind?
What is that pages? Yeah, yeah, my kiddies are sleeping. Oh, damn
Wow
She's always talking
For one day
She was really being like
Watch your tail dude remember what happened last time
Just like when you caught your cat on fire
Well, I remember essentially I told you like stage on fire spread it around your house
Your cat got in that candle
If you know your cat jumps on the table and you leave a candlelit on the table
I mean, it's kind of your fault. This is my spiritual space
And it's a stone table for grounding for the cards and you know
She's not supposed to be that cat does not care about that. Huh? That's wild
What the rules are she's a cat exactly?
But yeah, there's not actually rules
two
Yes, you both did except for she's. Oh
She said weeds my therapy I'm gonna smoke a blunt and then you're asking if you smoke in a blunt
Well, sir, I was busy or I didn't understand that didn't hear that
You were busy drinking too much soy milk
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
What is it you use the terms
We don't I don't understand it
That's between you and yourself, I don't know to tell you yeah, you repeat it what I said
But you didn't ask that you didn't answer the question you don't fuck you don't understand the difference like if I ask you a question
You make the claim then I ask you a question. It's supposed to answer it. You're not supposed to fucking just like repeat what I said
It's common conversation, it's not that hard dude
So I am you asked me to define what you were talking about. I don't know what I asked you to define
What the fuck that you just brought up that I asked you to find what you were talking about that that you
Said I said I repeated what you said and you said that I asked you to define
It's hard
Summer it's not my fault. It's being logical here
You got child brain
Summer knows what that is
Please explain it in small words like oh, you know like you small words and you say it so I can't you you're not gonna do it
Oh
Okay, I'll do it. Go ahead. Okay. Here's though. Okay fucking he did 20 minutes later. Go ahead said
I'm done. That's thank you exactly walking retarded sir
It's hard. It's hard. I'm not
going to. It's hard. You have to
know the game to play the game
and then once you understand the
game, you stop playing the game
and then you'll be on my level.
Okay, little buddy. It's okay.
Well, that's like saying like
once you understand like being
logical, you're you're ill
logical. No, that's not true.
You're always you're fucking
retarded and then you become
smart and I become retarded
I have no clue what you just said
Then you act like it yeah, I like that I challenge you you're still you're still don't know what the fuck you're talking about correct
You didn't tell you you you you literally said
Well, whatever okay explain what you said slowly don't the fuck you're talking about
Yes, I just I literally just did you do I have to do again really?
I literally learned to stop fucking are you gonna know what I really it's all right
I don't want to have to look
My favorite pussy
Brother you're retarded dog and I had to be rude, but you are coming
Oh, yeah
Tell me something smart, you know, let's go ahead. Good. Tell me something no one else knows
I'm smarter than you
No, I never claimed that you see that would be a pertinent proof of me. I never claimed to be a genius there
That's all I'm ten steps ahead of you. I never claimed it
What did you say summer? I told you about that right when I was in jail. I was walking through
Yeah, for some reason that popped in my head brown chicken brown
I got that fucking
Brown chicken brown cow
No, it's about chicken
Okay, you'll fuck yourself. I thought you were a genius
It's bound to come down. Wow. I tell you
I'm a genius done done more smarter than you
Wow
Bro, it's brown chicken brown cow brown cow made a foul. Whoa
Oh, look when you're in jail and you're just doing what you're doing. It's brown chicken brown cow. All right
This is a very annoying
Let the women talk I ain't going nowhere
Well, let's run that bitch boys and one guy's right. Whoever's talking the fuck out of here
Get the fuck out of here
Oh my bad, I didn't really
Yeah, I might as well leave
Seeing you might as well leave. I didn't know I didn't know was the word goes my dad
goes
Show him how you're from 63rd
No way, uh, let the
Hey, that's me from sixty thirty. Hey, but the road goes back on I'll leave because I don't know trouble with the ghost
He wants all the smoke
The road goes back on why are you kicking them?
Why'd you hit the wheel
Somewhere I can only imagine what I look like when I was that drunk stupid
Hey wait
That pig leg then yeah, stop showing it and stop fucking talking about it be about
Then over bits
It is talking about their shit be about their shit. You know, I might I'm you know, who knows what's gonna happen
I might like it
And you would like it. You definitely like it splintery and fucking bloody like fuck. That's right
gross
Nicely when you got a peg leg
Oh
Amazing at first I was like
I better I better walk a fine line because you might not have a leg
Yeah, that's a fake leg you always seen you walking around on
Here we go. I
Didn't see walking when I first met I didn't see walking anywhere
What you're doing there laying there looking at me
Yeah
Would you fuck summer?
No
Whoa, that's question, but thank you for asking
Small world
Fucking I also ain't thinking the crazy one either
and
How are you five feet tall with 300 pounds?
You're not going to stop me, so for your little ballad, you can say what you want, kid, I own all of you motherfuckers.
Summer is a hooker from hell. She claims to be five feet tall. She has to be on the bunk beds.
Every page is a freak. The base is a freak.
I
Gonna get it motherfucker US
Oh
You're gonna get it now
Trying makes fucking cycle
Is a loser
A wolfie boy is LD. The petafile is LD.
Groocible Ghost TY is Tony.
I'm gonna delete my account.
I can go on all day!
I can tell from here my name's Alexie and
No, what do you like to see when you fuck off summer? I doubt you're 300 pounds. I bet you're laughing what?
135 I apologize for
Wait, wait, how old I'll tell you wait like that
And one and a half it's
Wow five one
Are you? No, fast, but in a half-bit.
Oh, wow.
Five-two, maybe.
So you're a midget.
No, the half-bit.
You are very small.
I'm little.
You're little.
But I'll still kick your ass.
Let's run it. Let's run it.
Justine Shatterbox today, what's going on with you? I
Don't know why I'm here
And then people tell that they think that they got me I because I'm very sensitive to the gay and lesbian and trans
Movement and people think that I'm there's nothing you'll be and that you're on a gay channel
I have fought and done, and I have been in many pride parades, and I have fought as like a lot of things.
Justin, can you tell everyone how good I am?
Can I tell you something?
Nice forehead, Summer.
Tell them something, Justine, please.
You like my forehead?
Jay, yeah, he is a very amazing helper.
She helped me bring me and my father together
because my father did not know how I really thought
and I told him what I thought
and now my father and me are best friends.
So he brought me my father back in my life.
I'm gonna crash out.
I'm gonna be on your story.
I would agree with that. No, I would just like to inform the rest of the panel that I'm morally superior
For sure. Oh, you went beyond virtue signaling. You just went straight there. Oh, hey, just yes
So, you know the real ones heard you and all these shit. It's just kept talking over you just so you know
Pro pain and be quiet
Fucking thank you. You like propane. Oh, yeah, one you like propane and don't forget the accessories
Ghost is finna crash out
What goes is that true are you finna crash out? It's building up. It's building up. Is it?
Mm-hmm freighters roll up okay for God's sake
Trader Joe
Oh, do you like bait or now, Justine?
No, I'm just going to crush her on that forehead.
Roll up.
Yeah.
You sound like you're thinking I'm all for the gay and lesbians, but I'm sick of that trans community
That's funny that the nice calm person. Where are all the
It's still winning the argument
Wait, what are you arguing about ghost? Oh shit, you sound just like ghosts. You're not good. Who's talking?
What is this guy named?
Don't worry about me
Listen to the word that I am saying the nice humble voice is beating you no matter how loud
How would you fucking speak you fucking dick? How's that? Yeah, that's nice humility right there for you
There's that humble voice coming out
What do you think of what's your opinion on ghosts?
Don't talk about me.
What's your opinion on ghosts?
You know a good topic.
I think ghosts are assholes because they're always starting shit
but they don't want to like show themselves just to show the cow.
We're asking everybody in the chat.
What's your opinion about double up here?
Smell yeah, tell me all about it. You have an opinion. Oh, yeah, your opinion matter
What do you think about double about who?
What's his name?
Yeah, no, I'm asking you. Yes. Wolfman's asking you. What do you think about Dubwub?
I'm asking you a clarifying question. Who the fuck are we talking about? Is it Wolfman or the do-dub?
The guy whose name is Dubwub. I don't know. I could be a little clear. Dubwub. Is that his name right? Dubwub, what's that?
Dubwub. I don't see Dubwub.
I don't see it you fucking dumb dumb. Yeah, so he's being covered. He's yeah, he's kind of concealed by the little chat
Okay, he's kind of concealed now now. He's kind of getting so you got caught out. What the fuck what am I doing dumb dumb?
Nothing really down here the lower right-hand corner
Lower right hand corner, me mother fucker, what are you thinking about me?
Well, I can hear your voice, we'll fuck you, I don't even know what to do.
You seem kind of out of it tonight, are you good Ben?
Well, how much have you had to drink?
Well, no, you made the mistake, sir.
You said like I can see his name, he's right next.
No, no, we can all see his name.
You have to admit I could not see his name.
Yeah, exactly, what the fuck are you talking to, boy?
We can all see his name.
I'm away, I'm 10 steps ahead of you.
What are you sipping on?
I couldn't see his name, dumb dumb.
Hell yeah.
the
So am I wrong for I couldn't see his name. No, no, what do you think about you know what I think now you're gonna change it
Now you're gonna change it. I won that one. Let's get the second one
Go ahead. That wasn't uh, that wasn't you won that debate
That wasn't a debate. He's the best debater on all of you. What do you think about what do you think about this crucifix?
He's a mass debater. You like him?
I think he's extremely annoying
He turns the panel to shit
Let's run it if you don't like it, let's run it
Run it debate bros have serious insecurity issues
It comes from being unable to perform sexually ghost is finna cross out
I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I
All right
We all
Retarded
Wilson he's drunk kick him out fuck you. I like this guy
What do you think about the double of the head
I
Sounds like a black name
You said that I think this this fake ghost guy was talking about
Wanted to get with you or something you said that he's not a brother. What's up with that?
Not me
I'm married he could never get with me. Yeah, but you said he's not a brother
You made he's not black. You made he's not black. I'm married. I'm married. I'm not asking you if you're I don't go fuck
Are you married to a black man? Are you married to a black dude?
I am married to a black man. So you did throw it out there that he's not a brother. He can't get with you
He can't get with you
He didn't know what you were a little bit of a racist
Yeah, I mean you're married I'm married
She's told you that literally
I'm not talking to a black man
If that bothers you, that's not my son
She's told you that I don't like your racism
No, I'm not racist
I've been with white people, I've been with black people
I've been with every time I race it
You're not a brother
She's married to a black man.
Fuck up, ghost, fake ghost.
No, I'm not going to shut the fuck up.
Bitch ass mouth.
Yeah, you weren't talking, but guess what?
Oh, my God, you're not going to say that.
I can't stand this guy.
He's gay as fuck.
Yeah, it's a retard fest.
You don't have to fuck.
You're talking about this guy's gay as fuck.
How that's a claim
That's how you're gay you literally just demonstrated you're not gonna
Great idea JT, you know, yeah, I told you he was gonna do this
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Check it out yourself. Bro. You're crashing out right now like the whole fucking ship is how am I right?
Okay, how am I crashing out?
You're fucking crashing out, bro. You know what? I feel like
How am I how am I crashing out? Oh you guys that's me. It's not beat me. You know, he's already
Yeah
Yeah, I feel like some of this cat
Hey
Ask questions you you gave off
Now you're
I guess you know the difference between like so I'm going to wish you'd been in the past
Beneath me anybody else
That shit was that shit was easy anybody else the kid he's not impressed at all
Wait page sets up. I was gonna say that cat is not fucking happy. I bet page wasn't
Other bitches like oh, I can't hear you. You know, but you're gonna fucking
How are you doing page? What's going on? I'm part of the panel here. What's that? I can't hear you this fucking fake ghosts talking
What do you say? I guarantee you should leave in two minutes. Oh my god. Hey page. How you doing? All right?
I
Had to get one little at last word and then you know bitch
No, I got two minutes by the way. Shut the fuck up. He is copying you, right? So
page full card
One card one card Vicky animal card
You know, it's gonna be a damaged shame is when we pull your IP address and find out who you really are you need to really chill
Who are you talking to?
Yeah, go ahead and pull it.
Go ahead and pull it.
Pull it.
That would be the last time you pull anything.
Come over here.
Pull it.
Let's run that.
You can have a good time.
Pull it.
IGRG, that would be the last time you ever do anything.
Fucking pussy.
Pull it.
It's too lady
I can't hear you this fucking homos talk again. Yeah, fuck everybody. I don't miss this number. Oh, you think I'm yelling. I'm not yelling
I
Run it come over
Let's run that bitch talk
Let's run it you're not gonna run it so let's fucking debate them summer you're not gonna come over you know better
I heard someone
Can we debate about why you drink?
Curseable, yeah, I know I know Chris of all dog is it?
Right
You would you like me to give my address? I will
I don't miss
I don't miss come on. I did it all mine. I don't miss
Come on over see what happens. I don't want to come over to your house for what?
No, let's debate
I heard that I heard that I was busy. I'm here now. What should we do?
Get your son together get your son together
Page
Let's reset this whole panel
You got the weed okay good. She's about to pull out the cards and we're gonna see you right or take out the feather
Look what you did. I love that. Yeah
He's using the double feather
Yeah, we need probably all three of them to be real
We're gonna use these jips cars you're like a thousand years old and they're gonna tell you
I literally had to read a
These cars and they came with a pamphlet and they told me what it means
I'm actually, I'm actually a me, uh,
Yeah, sure.
There you go, Paige.
All I'm saying is that the, dude, the cards came with the pamphlet, right?
That's a stage, dude.
Or what?
Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
Do you really think anyone on this panel, rather than you, over Paige?
Dude, am I tripping or is Dobs in, like, crucible, like, two versions of the same guy?
It does seem like there's three of them on the panel right now.
If you think you got real good
Maybe we're talking the same shit. So maybe not the real one
That's wild. Yeah, I think you might all be
Being crucible in the same time
No, no, no, they share
That's my brother. Oh, I'm saying is there nobody gonna run over here. I guess you know, I'm saying is that that that
Amendment year
That came with a big brother. Oh, you had to read them
Boss us around
Go ahead go ahead now this will be good
the
that's the shall receive
that's God
What the fuck so I get it together here. We go here. We go here. This is good
This is good. I was the one to ask we got seven. I look like a Canadian goose feather
And this is an eagle feather from the Peppers Lake and this is also you put peppers like I
Mean damn she told me
And I'm supposed to think you're not on pills like like what the fuck man
Where are you psych
He said the panel shunt down at one o'clock
So we better hurry up
I thought we say and then we do a reading it's almost one right now. It's 12 o'clock almost
Is it 1248
Shit, it's almost 1 a.m. Hey, you're not to hurry up, please
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Don't rush it. Don't rush. I don't I don't think that I like
You gotta me watch you owe me well everybody was yelling so I yelled I had to yell louder
Yeah, but your volumes down
I just want to be clear
For the record
You're about what some of you guys I was not yelling
You have any feathers there are a lot of people yelling I don't yell
I
Had some
Oh, you you got the dream catch you so the summer kind of yells I heard just shout out to Vinny pots and pans
Well, you're making
Like I was like
I'm young young the cat is crazy
Who is young young the cat come on
I've dated all that's how these stop
You're breaking up as that I say she's not a racist
Chill out, but what deck is this page you're not you're busy. I
Don't go about a killer I go by personality
Yeah a couple days ago
No, I didn't say it 20 minutes ago. You just did yes, you did. Okay, whatever. We're not gonna do a whole ghost thing over here
That's what you want to do. We need stage
We just got staged
Got paged now we're getting paged
That is the ones to get paged
No, we're not talking about that
You can't put what they say in Haiti does not listen so
Listen too well, I think it's a problem
Look at that
They sleep so comfy. Look at that
Her name is baby girl
Baby girl, but I'll call her baby a lot baby girl
Okay, so this is just a collective read rate. So everybody's gonna resonate with this card
I'll spread everybody you may or may not
But you can take something that resonates with you. It's not
And if it doesn't then don't or you don't or something that doesn't fit
Possible to turn her up. I don't know why but I'm being told to
Turn people to be open-minded not people that are yeah, maybe to new people
Thank you. Can you turn her mic up a little bit?
I mean she can do it. Yeah, hold on
She's talking to you ghost go go to 130 page go to 130
Just put it to math is that better
Where you at? What's the number? What's the number of just throw it all the way up?
Yeah, the whole way up might work
We can hear your refrigerator hold on that's kind of crazy
It's like hold on. It's yeah, just echo cancel and then just put that all the way up
Can you hear me now? Yeah
Probably as good as it's gonna get
Yeah
We got eight minutes
Don't rush her
seven minutes
were running out of time
seven minutes as you've got seven
I'm not rushing around six minutes
why did he say that it was closer than one
he said, he said it
he did not
he did
just pretend like he didn't
look I'm gonna look back in the chat
oh the elk
the buck
oh that's you Denison, that's you
why is he Denison
Oh, a running buck?
He just admitted it.
Well, I was trying to think like you.
Good luck.
I think I nailed it father. The great elk represents the earth element. It's mass to inform
This means underlying support and stability amidst life's many change or changes and challenges an elk personality
Whether male or female is fully established in themselves and knows their care their core values and them like their true self
They become and are known and respected for acting in ways that uphold these values at all times.
Sometimes the Elx ego can become inflated though, but for the most part they make
To make damn good fathers mothers lovers and friends all that's nice isn't it yeah, goddamn right the world needs more elk energy
So when in balance it's supportive kind and consistent when out of balance
Pretentious and a high and mighty
That is me to be fair
I could just pull on for it of these for people tonight. I don't know if you
Pretentious audience yes, it is it really is
I'll take one
I always enjoy reading you summer
I think she's gonna get a bird
Okay, so yeah, you guys can all like guess
Yeah, I think I think she's got some kind of
That's what I normally do with this deck is like kind of the
Maybe a flower
Do they have insects?
Oh, it's animals
Maybe if those are animals too
Okay, so
A flower is an animal
Well, no the insect
Yeah, there's insects
There's like the odd like mythical thing and then there's every other animal except for like oh like a unicorn
An ard vark aren't in there
Ard vark
Ladybug
There's maybe I think there might be one but maybe not I'm sensing like an eagle
Okay, okay
Place your bets. What about chat? We got a
What about like a brain-eating amoeba?
You psyche was a gross thing that you showed us that one time that like cat hair space. You've got four minutes
No, no
Now he said that he was gonna let it go as long as
Okay, what do you think it's gonna be it wasn't falling out because nobody was done yet
Not like I just want to pick the top card that's not how we do this boom there you go
That was a special bird look at that bird. It's an egg. See
I told you a phoenix. Oh my
god. Maybe we shall let him do
the cards. I have a phoenix on
my back. I bet you do. I do.
I did see it. Beautiful.
It's perfect.
Right, it could be more perfect. It's fucking awesome. Okay, then there's this motherfucker reborn. I like shark
Sharks are cool
The three of these and I guess I'll have to resonate with somebody
That was the the shark is ghost
I like sharks
You like sharks. Yeah. I like sharks. I like sharks. Sharks are cool. It's shark weeks. Yeah. I like shark weeks. Shark. Take a bite out of that.
I remember that. I used to be so stoked for it. Okay, Summer, I'm going to do the cool next verse. That was a good movie, that Meg. Okay.
Let's see the Meg. First one was good. There's the egg again. How does an egg even count? It's a bird.
Are you the one that's a flower?
That was me. What is it? Okay? You guys are being oddly cute
So message at the center of the heart. I have a girlfriend page. I'm sorry. I'm not hitting on you
I'm just your enemies. I'm just saying like I don't I'm never gonna go ahead
She was talking to me anyway. Go so you know
Nah, she
What I'm sorry
it's just a very cute panel right now so it's very dull
I'm in a playful mood, it's what have JT brings it out
it was not in place to be 10 minutes to 20 minutes ago and now it's gone
oh we had the fake ghost there
yeah cause yeah all the queers are gone that's why
yeah the fake ghost was here
I mean you know
that's the wrong word for what was going on but
bundle of sticks
The message at the center of the heart, the unstruck sound.
Within the golden egg lives a precious sound deep within the sound resides a message.
The sound cannot be heard nor the message discerned until we retreat from the noise
of modern-day life.
The magical essence of the golden egg needs warmth, quiet, and time to unfold.
No rushing, pushing, or grasping.
Well, like anything you do that comes you summer, so smoke and dope would do fine
If you
Not yet have a meditation practice take some time for introspection and contemplation
When the mind begins to settle and breathe is like and you can use your breathing to settle and use that calm
Do you know the breathing methods? I know that's like Marcy's backstage
Yeah
Okay, so ask the question that weighs heaviest on your heart staying open to any response that you hear
Engaging with the energy of the golden egg is an advanced practice.
It requires becoming intimate with our very essence and comfortable with vulnerability.
When a feeling of tenderness or gratitude arises from deep within you, know that you are well on your way.
Your tests may swell like you are seeing an old friend that's been away for a long time.
Listen to the message they've been waiting to tell you.
Look at it see it's a little person and it's little egg and that's
full
It's just
No more babies
So freedom from suffering past karma and reincarnation the Phoenix represents the transformation of our past
It doesn't mean running from it, denying it, or burning bridges with rage.
The Phoenix, oh, employs an advanced technique described in yoga as the burning of impurities
through practice and dedication.
The essence of the Phoenix is with us when we realize we have been suffering for too
long and something must change.
We take a stand and we decide to live consciously instead of being driven by the unconscious mind
and its long list of fears and aversions. At that very moment the spark of the phoenix is lit
and the great bird helps us burn through our baggage. We no longer run from who we are
and what has happened to us or what we have done. The stuckness and the dead weight fall into the
ashes and the brightness and the clarity emerge as this pregnancy continues.
To smolder, the phoenix lifts our spirits up and up and we begin to recognize ourselves.
Again, we may catch a glimmer in our eye that wasn't there before.
Look closely, it's a sign of the fire and the transformation is upon your wings.
Oh, that was beautiful. That was
perfect. Yeah. That was very
fitting for you. Summer and of
course, they came out together
and they go together and they're
like right next to each other
in the book. Marcy.
What up?
Pretty Marcy. Okay.
Who is Marcy? Marcy.
Go ahead. I'm just gonna find it. You can talk. Do you think?
Here's the shark. Yeah, it goes, but it goes with the shark.
The shark? What happened? Beautiful.
We're doing cards
Revealing true nature and desire
The shark is only dangerous when we don't acknowledge it. This card indicates that something big needs to be exposed
It's lurking in the depths and creating tension shark energy takes over when we are hesitant to be honest
To be totally ourselves or to say what we really want
It may be tempting to continue pretending nothing is wrong, but when a shark
Energy is at play. We feel its presence in circling us when in balance
Intriguing captivating was serious when out of balance sneaky and disruptive and to bring into balance honesty
I'll take it okay
Okay
Sure, I've never had a card pulled from me
Oh
Page was my first to be gentle
She was gentle
I'm ready for it. She likes it rough. Wow
We gotta go for a ride
And jogging?
Yeah, I'm going to jog them. No
Are you going to need paper, smoke, or food?
Mm-hmm. Oh shit.
Hmm.
Are you like
doing some sort of like, are you dividing something and maybe it's an uneven divide or going through like something of that nature?
It's fine. Not that I can do a rabbit. She's gonna get a rabbit. No, no, it's not a big thing. I don't know. What is it?
Or like a blockage of some sort because when my cars do that, that's why I do it like this, you guys.
I was trying to get up on panel for a while. That was a little frustrating.
Yeah, they're fine now. It was
saying studio full, studio full,
studio full for like 10 people
up here. Yeah, 10 people were
already up here. What do you
say? Holy shit, that flip like
in no time. It flips so pretty
too. Wait, is somebody else
trying to get up here? I'll
jump. No, no, no, you're good.
No, you can you can jump good.
Kitty
What did she get what do you think a rabbit
Is she
Did I get a rabbit I thought my husband went to sleep
I have no problem with bugs. I have no problem with spiders either unless they land on me and then they might die
Even if they go in front of my face and I could see him, I'll get rid of him, but I'm not afraid of spiders.
You couldn't live what I do.
Lions and tigers and bears on my house.
Right?
Oh my god, the cheetah and the tiger just came through the lion.
He's saying that.
Where the fuck is it?
I'm a Leo!
Maybe?
Fucking bug.
Oh, he's no way.
I got it. We're good.
cut my veins. I think I cut them too short. We do it for ourselves too guys.
Add a crossroad in claiming life's purpose. The tarantula represents a moment when a great
decision must be made. It involves prioritizing your life's deeper purpose or your dharma.
A habit or routine from the past is sidetracking your friends' dreams.
Yet a voice inside keeps begging you to refocus your attention.
In order for you to find true happiness, you must choose Dharma.
Until you do, satisfaction will be fleeting.
The tarantula hovers as patience can come with an old friend that knows your inner soul.
It already knows you'll choose wisely.
When imbalanced follows intuition, when out of balance hesitates and over intellectualizes,
You bring into balance daily
journaling. We'll bring it into
balance. I guess that's what
start journaling. Okay, in chat.
I can't do it in chat. No, it
is Dharma. She's like a black
widow. No, she's not. No, I
She mates and then she kills
No
The principles of order law and moral duties
My Dharma
Yeah, like enlightenment, right? It's a duty
That's the goal, okay, they're on tpp. Oh shit
I knew they were gonna end up over there. They were over there earlier. Yeah. Oh, where were they? Oh shit
Are you behind? I am we're over here
They're over here. Excuse me
Are you giving me shit? Oh shit, I know who it is. That's doing that. Okay
Okay, you know Trump is
Who's I know who Trump is who is from thank you Trump for coming in and saying something
I wouldn't have known except for seeing you use voice changer before it's a voice box. Oh
You think you know who I am
Everyone's not a voice box. It's a voice box, and I'm like don't we all have voice boxes
Just me
that
Yeah
You can tell that it's a bit because he was hyper focused on one of the qualities of Trump's voice
That's how you can know it's
Like the the raspy kind of trailing the high pitch
You know like
His tone is very meandering and he gets high-pitched when he meanders instead of low-pitched
That's one of the unique things about his voice
You know most people trail off and they get like quieter and lower Trump gets higher
Way trails that when he meanders can I get my animal cut?
The city's always asking a question right right exactly. Yes, it sounds like he's asking a question all the time exactly
So if it's doing that accurately why wouldn't
Because an AI is gonna it will approximate his actual voice that was moving not the comic not the comic qualities of his voice
It wouldn't even understand
It doesn't have the nuance like right
Right in the in the nuance when you're doing a comedic bit you overemphasize the nuance right like you hit it every time and you overdo it
For this they could easily make it do that. Oh, this she is welcome back
No, no you fell off
Well, just like you just pick me out
Take you back
The spider that's the kitty with the two color eyes are like sitting right off stage and then waiting for me to make the right choice
You're like a spider
I am like a spider. I am like a spider.
You're like spinning a web. What's up my eight legs?
That's your sticky web.
I don't, I don't favor trail behind. Sticky web, wow.
I was like, ugh.
I was a little gross. It's nail trail? No thanks.
Ew. Really?
I knew it. I knew it the whole time. All of you guys were you. Like you all knew. Like exactly what I was talking about. Oh my god. My ex has been ruined my brain. He's up there with Gemini too. Oh yeah, Gemini and Trump.
When I was like 19 and the girls she put the she like all the girls were walking around half-naked with little like
bandanas on their shoulders
And she I pick one to like give me my first dance or whatever
She brings me back into the room and she puts her little bandana on my lap
And I'm like what's this for and then she takes her panties off and I'm like, oh
The reason for the hanker chip is so there is nothing left on your pants
This nail trail thing we're the inspiring
I
We done with the cards
I love another card. Yeah, we'll do something different for you
Yeah, I want the animal card after after that
You want an animal card?
Yes, please
Some animal crackers
Have animal crackers they got the giraffe
Animal crackers in my soup, animal crackers in my soup.
No you don't have to do that. That's okay.
He went there.
I thought he was going to stop.
He danced himself off stage.
That's an omen. A good omen.
He was like with his top back right off dance right off the right off. Yep jazz hands
It was funny, dude. He was getting frustrated. Oh, he's getting mad. He's still mad
Who it Alex yeah, you don't read that
Oh
Yeah, they're there in purgatory
That's what I call it
Yeah, we have so much in common now. Right? Oh my god. This part is this? We're like the same now. Marcy. Oh Marcy. Yeah. Oh my gosh you guys. Oh that's Raven's card. She's flashing all the pussy on camera. Hey? Yeah my god. I'll put the in the sauce. Okay. Right on cam. Bam. Pussy pussy.
They just want to party and so 35 the number 35 could be significant Marci in some way, but education came out in the upright for you.
Okay, education.
So are you going to
Like, are you upgrading or are you trying to-
I'm not going to school, no.
I always, I always further educate myself.
I'm kind of a nerd that way.
It doesn't, yeah.
This doesn't have to be education
when pertaining to school.
Like, you could literally just be like an autodidact.
You just love to read books.
You could love to just find information out.
You just eat it, right?
Yeah.
I like medical studies too.
I like reading medicine.
There you go.
Okay, well I'll read but I'll just I could be a doctor but yeah, but we also have
Protecting treasure in the reverse number 39 could mean something to you. I'll show you this in the upper right
She's laying on like a treasure chest and has an umbrella over her and she's getting it's getting rained on
She's protecting it though, but it's in the reverse. Then we have metamorphosis coming out in the upright
So did cars and the number 25 could be significant as well as 30. Yeah, if you add all three of those numbers together
That's how old I'm turning next week
I'll be 43
23rd
I thought you were going to say it was the 8th time you had your 35th birthday
I got a big present for you
My oldest sister always tells everyone that she's 35
When I passed 35, I was like dude, you're 14 years older than me
You cannot get away with me 35 anymore
I've been buying my nana to happy 29th birthday cards since I was like 10
She's been 29 forever.
Beans is a chunk of chunker.
Beans is a chunky spunk of chunk.
Your little belly is always swinging.
You should see her run.
It's hilarious.
And she sounds like she's wearing high heels in the house.
Like a teacher or principal.
Okay.
Beans got her hair stuck to me.
Cats now.
Hey, hey, hey, can I just tell you guys something I just wanted to come up here and say that you guys might not know JT or Goddy, but they I have known them for many years, and they are very amazing people.
That is what I'm coming up here to say.
That's why it popped up here in the first bit.
But sometimes they could be a little gruff and around their edges, but they are very good people
Why are you fucking come up here saying all that I don't know if I can hang out with weirdos like that
Justin we
I'm sure you guys went over this grid.
Page is in the middle of a reading, too, by the way, Christine.
No, but she's right though about the other stuff
Yeah, nobody told you to add okay, justine you're not supposed to just
Stick to the script. She's absolutely right
Yeah, you're not getting paid for this this isn't improv class, okay
Never. You did great Justine. I like that.
Alright, what was next?
Don't listen to them.
Hey, she's giving me a reading guys.
No, it's really fine. Like we can do this like later on. I can go to mine and do one for you.
I didn't get my animal card.
I will give you your animal card. Okay, so the long story short you guys
Marcy it's like you're wanting to further you're doing you're have a big idea you'd want to do something
I think that I'm not trying to poke, but I'm are you a little bit bored?
You're ready to transform you're ready for something new not like a new really kind of yeah
You're just getting antsy I think and you've been protecting something up for a long time
And maybe it's a bit of trauma that's not allowing you to move. I've been in a lot of pain for a long time
and now I'm finally getting my body back and like April's are like
Like metamorphosis like you're becoming like it's like a butterfly. Do you know what I mean?
So I really really encourage yeah like look at this and this making choices thing keeps coming up
for you like something about having two decisions to make. I'm sorry I'm really bad. No it's okay.
It's cool.
Yeah, like I don't know this one's my favorite though
Like there's been a lot of there's been a lot of downtime with that introspection
You know what I mean? You had to learn a lot about your your health conditions
It's kind of what sparked you and like you've always had an act for this
But it sparked you to kind of discover more about yourself
Which is what a lot of these cards are that came out including the tarantula and and protecting something guarding something
But also knowing your purpose and
That you doing those things actually helps you more than any doctor can or anybody else can because you have to listen. Yeah
Right, especially with american healthcare. Oh my god. You don't even know exactly
So you're like you've relied on yourself
Done this for a long time by yourself
You know what I mean in the sense of having to go through these things and not being understood
Sometimes under waiting for answers or people or
It's just, it's been a big fuck around game, right?
And you spend your life and your physical health
and it's just really kind of been it.
You want to live, Marcy.
You're just ready to live.
You're ready to just like move forward
with a bunch of things.
You have options that you're thinking about.
And I do think that that if you have,
you're going through a transformation,
you're coming out of this ghost land bullshit,
finding that home within yourself.
You know, it's beautiful.
I love it.
Cool.
That's for you.
I've been thinking about the cards that you've already read, and I think I know what that
decision making is, and I come to kind of a crossroads type of thing, I understand that.
Well then, does that make sense? Honestly, I could have channeled for it in hardly half of
use occurrence, but we were demanding. Yeah. I'd love to, I'd love to get into, like, I'd love
to do a deeper reading for you, a more meaningful one that's kind of more personal. Cool. That'd be
awesome. And pertaining to some of your health conditions and answers that you're looking for,
and maybe we can work together and find some of them for you. Cool. Yeah.
There you go. Awesome. Thank you. You're welcome anytime anytime you want to hop in and just say hey, bitch
I want a car, please
Bitch, I want a card. That's I'm gonna say it just like that. You better say it just like that like summer comes in hot
Right. Hey
No, we're not
That's what makes that's like the flavors of life, right? Like no vanilla beautiful. Yeah, you have to have lots of flavor and in that you have to have bland and exciting because well, we just need that mix in a while like you said, the lamest way I've ever said that but okay, I'm still on now we're having fun and I'm tapped in so I feel like like had a delirium.
Are you gonna guess what you think it is first
What do you guys think well, what's gonna be my
Frog
Oh
Yeah, that's a reptile
Oh that turtles are very wise
Okay, so then you got a moth the same color so moth
If a moth got with the turtle, it would be a frog, right?
I'm just kidding.
It would be a...toth?
Tooth?
A mertle?
A mertle or a toad?
I don't know.
A mertle.
A frog?
Well, it would be.
Okay.
Depends if it got the wings or if it got the shell, right?
100% Marcy.
100%.
I don't know. I don't know if I've ever read the moth in here. The moth, the moth balls.
Well, the moth seems very mysterious.
Trivia, quick trivia. Do you know why people put moth balls in their closets?
Goo Goo Gaga.
Just stop moths from eating the clothes.
Yes.
No, let's give it all that shit. It's simple.
Goo Goo?
That's why you should use Cedarwood instead.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's a natural inhibitant to moths.
Dude, this isn't heating.
Oh, it is?
Nope, we're in here.
It's also resistant to moisture and rot.
Goo Goo, gotcha.
Misted.
Somebody's writing it in the chat.
Oh, okay. So, impulsive, hasty, and wishful.
The moth is always sure the grass is greener on the other side.
Moth energy is at play when we're attracted to easy solutions or anything shiny and new.
This can lead to unfinished projects, disappointment, or burnout.
It's helpful to remind moth personalities that life is complex.
No matter the illusion, no one is exempt from the trials and tribulations of this great journey.
Practice seeing life as an infinite mystery rather than this wishing that it was easier different
So when in balance, enthusiastic whimsical
When out of balance, oh, I you like I idolize others or idealize them
Sorry jittery to break into balance finish a project
So finish what you start
Builds confidence within you
apparently
I just opened up to the frog. That's crazy
You guys all said it so many times that happened
We made it happen
It's actually right behind the turtle the turner the frickin frogs gay ladies and gentlemen
I've got the documents
So an ancient soul grounded trusting and at home in the cell
it is wonderful to be in the presence of a turtle personality. Like the beaver, the turtle has
strong relationship with the earth and water elements simultaneously. This helps to ground
and connect them to the deeper truths of life. No matter where their travels lead them, turtle
energy is behind all great writers and storytellers, as they collect life experiences under their
shells for later use. The most potent turtle energy helps us close all of the other books and begin
When in balance peaceful adventurous and productive when out of balance it slows down to a halt
So kind of just paralyzed to bring into balance on go on an adventure
Okay
Nice, I like that. Thank you. You're welcome
It's cool that they came out together and they actually are just like
One kind of solidifies the other. It's like here, you know, this is the idea and here's the wings time to fly
What's teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle would you be?
Me who you're asking page or me?
Yeah
Which one do you think I would be I shut that shit right down
TPP I just shut TPP down
Well, what did you do that fool Gemini said I'm God. I'm God. I said fuck you. You've got
No panel down
Were you over there now? No, no, I just shut it down from here. Oh with like your powers or something my powers
Yeah, that's it
What do you think about a birthday magician? I got a little magic
Yeah, I do. Yeah. Well, you're wrong. Shut it down every night
Always forget there's so many friends of that douchebag here like
Not friends
It's over you're gonna join in the factory I thought I thought I was gonna get one
Just give me the top card. Just give me the top card the top card the top card
Bam no, you can't cuz it's the turtle and it's cuz I just said okay. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, we do it redo it
Well, I just thought we were done. I thought you guys were getting bored cuz it was starting to get rowdy again
No, I was waiting my turn, but somebody kept talking
See and the mouse beneath it. What is that?
It's a eagle to kept saying eagle and I just was nosy and I just flipped it while I want to go
Yeah, you watch me do it. I didn't do it on purpose the grandest of all birds
Okay, I don't know about that
We don't know about that. What do you think the grandest bird is because actually there's quite a few different ones
Yeah, what would we rank what would you rank ahead of it?
An owl an owl is the smartest of all birds
Very wise
Condor is more brand no ego will kill a condor
Eagle can't even kill a Canadian goose
Maybe that's the most superior bird
Canadian goose
Maybe probably not you silly goose
Oh, he just rose from the dead look at this
Did a little bump
He's good to go I did a line it'll be up for four hours now
I didn't notice this. I didn't notice this thing. Hey Pat, I think I'll carry you.
Oh, Marcy's backstage. She fell off. Okay. Marcy, I'm not like trying to keep it.
Okay, before when I was trying, it docked me out, and then I came as soon as I could, and then it's like, yeah, I'm sorry.
The other guy went wrong on my end like I don't know what happened. It says something went wrong. Yeah
You did the right thing one second one second there you go a little is this
This are you there?
This okay, she's not there. Okay, so that was maybe a
Liz talk to me in chat. Tell me that you're like there or I can't like bring you up unless I have you're like
It takes like a minute for
Give me a sign, Liz. She's in Australia. Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, she didn't say
Sometimes when they don't say anything they're like trying to form up. I guess I'll try again. Hold on
I was thinking the other night. I was like damn you have more mom more than anyone. I think I've ever seen
Yeah, it might be George campaign over a hundred times
Probably perfect was like 200 now that I've only been double once I eat
Including failed attempts
Yeah
I mean no, no, no, I had like a hundred people successfully go through and like for Bob like probably about a hundred
Probably about 200 attempts or three hundred attempts. I don't know. It's like I kind of get more than I
Attempts than I do actual successes now
maybe one time a day
But then we should play some trivia. I'll even fucking get off here
I'll go write down all the trivia questions like I do normally or I'll just like
Going to flip back and forth and I cut out as it is, but I want to play trivia. I'm
Sorry. No, not you.
It's fine.
So all pervading tower truth seeker transforms karma.
The noble eagle emanates the light of the sun.
This great bird is both physically and spiritually strong
and represents mastery over the elements of fire and air.
When the eagle appears, you'll soon be thrown into the karmic fire
for the sake of your transformation.
The eagle pushes us to do to be our best and brightest selves.
and stops at nothing to see us shine. Grasp the sun in your talents and hold on for the ride.
You are stronger than you think, evil child. When in balance, bright, radiating challenges,
when out of balance, controlling. To bring into balance, step into the unknown.
That's insane the peacock and the hummingbird. I'll show you guys this is crazy totally describes me so this one was like
This one these were just all like this when I went to go move the duck so it's not the panther anyways
This is cool. It was the eagle the peacock and the hummingbird
Now it smells like bird arm, that's great.
Anyway, bird hair is one of the worst, you know.
I know, and it feels weird, it feels bald now.
Birds in a ball.
Toasted.
Hey, at least you don't have to get a waxing on your arms.
No, I'm like, I'm toasted for you.
Can't fire a Canadian marshmallow now.
It's so tempting to just ban him from like, well,
Tiffany, just do it.
I'm gonna smoke some more weed before I play trivia.
You better help me.
Thanks, Paige.
You're welcome, guys.
Hey, yo.
Yeah, thank you.
You're welcome.
I love y'all.
Assholes.
I love you too, too, too, too, too.
Okay, let's put this away, Paige,
instead of leaving your shit all over your own stuff,
please.
I'll ship them anywhere in the U.S. I've got like five running through the living room
right now just like fucking going crazy like they're ready to run into walls and ships
Hey, that was that was he
My brother right there
Look at this mess
How does this happen this is what happens when those headphones these what my kid does stuff
That's crazy. It's my daughter did that to you. I always got her blue tooth once after she did that a couple of times
She has blue tooth ones. She loses those and then she has to steal these. These are mine. I actually yeah, and then
She does this with them when she finds
I got her head first
I just got her headphones and it works way better just the Bluetooth headphones though like
Doesn't have to deal with or the ones that have like the
The thing she could put her out her neck like it just you know, and it has to have phones on one wire
That seems to be pretty
child's face
Yeah chords like that remind me of being a kid
Like what we always had like like a drawer full of fucking different wires that went dead like all kinds of different shit
My dad always thought he was gonna fix whatever broke. So like
Dude when he passed away there were like 20 fucking weed whackers in the shed on like various states of disappear
You can fix all of these?
Okay, I don't think I know what this is for, oh.
Maybe it has to survive in Star Trek.
What was that?
What?
You didn't touch that either.
Was he sneak talking?
You're gonna survive in Star Trek, is that what he said?
Did he just slaughter the wall in like one word?
I'm pretty sure if you can survive in Star Trek, you're alright.
That's what he said, right? Can I like do you think the first three Star Wars are the best and the last middle is shit
And the fucking like
That's an unpopular opinion too.
Wow, really?
Yeah, it is. It's a really unpopular opinion, but I'm gonna share it.
Well, I think I like Star Wars.
I don't like the Beatles either.
I hate the Beatles.
Fucking Beatles suck.
I don't like the Beatles either.
Yeah, I do like the stones.
Yeah.
I'm more of a stones person than the Beatles.
I'm more of like a Pink Floyd person.
Oh my god.
I love Pink Floyd.
But I prefer rap and hip hop.
So.
Really?
Definitely.
I really do.
Kendrick Lamar.
Yeah.
Drake Daddy.
Oh, dude, there's like a trick daddy. I couldn't even fuck in.
I don't like a trick daddy.
Do you see that?
Do you know it?
Like ludicrous. I like a lot of what the truck.
I don't see that.
Yeah, that's cool.
I love that.
I love employee with a passage.
This is in my bathroom on the bottom door.
This is my door.
I love Pink Floyd with a passion. I do. Yeah, I saw him in I saw him in the planetarium and the
Laser light show and oh my god. It was the best thing I've ever seen in my life
My ex husband's uncle saw them like everywhere. He was probably at that show like
All over all over he saw all kind of music is my passion in life
It's my one passion.
It's like definitely like a feeling, I would say.
Like when I'm in pain or when I like do something like garden or like do something fun.
I listen to hip-hop and rap music and like pump myself up like I like it.
I call it hip-hop therapy.
I call it electronic therapy for me because I like electronic music.
Yeah, but I love hip-hop too. I'm not kidding you. I do. Yeah
I do
I love dr. Dre and I love Snoop Dogg in the 1990s
Yeah
Hey, you want to know something I saw Jay-Z and concert man and the Pemberton Festival
I saw Jay-Z and concert when was that?
And the Pemberton Festival in British Columbia, like in, I don't know, 2007, 2008.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for the super chat, Tiffany.
Thank you so much.
Oh, she just paid that tab.
Justine kicked off for two minutes.
Okay, bye, Justine.
We'll see you in two minutes.
I think you make that up
No, that's what she does
That's all she can afford
You're never finding me broke bitch
You know what Tiffany does Tiffany wraps out people she's a wrap so that's what she is she's a rat
I don't know. Who is she?
Find them all or you know.
She'll sell your soul down the river. Trust me. She's a river seller.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Out of respect
Middle in middle, bro. Fuck it Alex Wiley backstage
Wasting $50
I'm kicking somebody off a panel for two days.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, that was...
That'd have to be some like...
She's very tempted to get me banned for life.
I said, just don't...
Indulge yourself.
Why be tempted?
Just do it.
Just do it. Jump off the ledge.
Jump off the ledge. I've been told that.
Because I bungee jumped. I bungee jumped. I bungee jumped twice.
Wow. If I weren't done that last year, my neck would have fallen off.
My head would have been attached.
That's not good. That's not good.
No, no, no.
That's a horrible way to say that.
But we can laugh at it now.
We can laugh at it now.
I know what the bungee cord is not supposed to be wrapped around your head though, okay?
Just for your, for your knowledge.
I should have told that to my pain management doctor.
What's your next thoughts from the wake last?
What's your favorite chocolate bar?
I don't know. I don't know.
It's got like pistachio butter in it, and it's got some...
They don't like people like me and Dubai.
It's a straight five, bro.
And by people like me, I mean poor people.
I don't like poor people.
I just said I'm poor. I'm too.
They don't like...
Especially because I'm Canadian and poor.
You're right. I'm American. You know what, and I'm indigenous so like I've got all three things that people are like, I don't like, I don't know about you.
Wow, so you're, so your personation is cool.
It's cool.
That is so cool. I love that.
Yep, thank you
So you really don't even know what to believe anymore growing up in American schools like they didn't teach us shit
Then you truly are Canadian
I come from Abbotsford, have you ever heard of that?
Yeah, well I'm from Kelowna, well I'm back in Kelowna
Oh my god, oh my god, Kelowna is fucking amazing
It's got the most amazing art gallery, I love Kelowna
She was super excited about that, Kelowna, huh?
Yeah.
I don't think I can even get into Kelowna.
I got two DUIs, though.
Kelowna and Victor.
Yeah, I used to plant churches with my church group.
I used to plant churches back in the day.
And so we were trying to plant a church in Kelowna,
and it took off because we went there like every weekend,
like telling the neighborhood going door to door.
Yeah, I used to do that.
I was 24 years old when you left.
How you mean?
Jesus Christ, what I've been through.
Do you think you were a Jehovah's Witness?
No way!
I don't know, you said you were planning a church. I've never heard that.
Yeah, planning a church.
Planting a church is in my, in my little church that I used to go to. I won't talk to myself.
They would go to places, they would go to, they would go,
plant a church and then they would go door to door telling people about that new church.
Are you saying, are you just saying, are you saying, are you saying plant as in PLAN or plant as in PLAN?
Is it planning a church?
Yeah, it's planting, right?
She's planting.
Yeah, with a T.
Planting.
No
You clarified that but yeah, I was like Joe's witness. I was starting to think those door-to-door dudes
And then I was like, I don't know enough about a job as witness to know they say they
Before she hated God just didn't tell everyone how great I am
You are you help me so much
I love JT, JT, JT, she brought me and my father back together and we helped each other out.
He's amazing person and he's also caring and very knowledgeable and gave me some good advice
that I just took and who would have thought it figures, but truthfully I really did
Pick up some good advice and I took it and he was right
Who was a vice from again?
I am Canadian. Do you see how I did that too? Yeah. That's my thought about it. We are sisters of another province, another country.
What do you want to do?
Trivia
What's what's the trivia?
Multiple subjects
Well, we can just do whatever man stuff. I don't think I've ever done
Sikes usually pretty good with asking trivia questions. Normally, I'll have some written down, but I could leave and go do that
When I come back and ask you the questions, but also sake has cards and we all have the internet
And I only have one device so I can't let's switch back and forth
All right, did somebody else ask questions or
Hey, can you give me a car
I almost love getting readings. I mean, I've just never had a reading before, so I love hearing other people's readings, though. It's so interesting to me.
We have to bounce back. There's probably some people in the chat that are going to be angry that Trivia's been further delayed.
Chat? That's what happens when you don't come on panel. It's the same.
Sorry, I shouldn't be like that. I love Chad. Chad's always right.
If that's all right with everybody because it's not they don't want to hear me babble
But we enjoy you with
This is a takeover take it over